https://www.thefusecompany.com/privacy-policy.php

The Fuse Company - If We Don't Have It, They Don't Make It!
BS88 CENTRE BOLTED TAG FUSES 125AMP TO 315AMP
TYPE 133mm FIXING CENTRESBUSSMANN (EATON) BS88 RANGE EFS TYPE 133mm CENTRE BOLTED TAGS FUSES
BS88 CENTRE BOLTED TAG FUSES 125AMP TO 400AMP TYPE 111mm
FIXING CENTRESBUSSMANN BS88 RANGE DD.ED TYPE 111mm CENTRE BOLTED TAGS FUSES
BS88 CENTRE BOLTED TAG FUSES 2AMP TO 100AMP TYPE 111mm FIXING CENTRESTYPE AD,TBC,BC,TB,CD,TC
BS88 CENTRE BOLTED TAG FUSES 355AMP TO 400AMP
TYPE 133mm/184mm FIXING CENTRESBUSSMANN (EATON) BS88 RANGE EF TYPE 133/184mm CENTRE BOLTED TAGS FUSES
BS88 CENTRE BOLTED TAG FUSES 450AMP TO 800AMP
TYPE 133mm/184mm FIXING CENTRESBUSSMANN (EATON) BS88 RANGE FF TYPE 133/184mm CENTRE BOLTED TAGS FUSES
BS88 NEUTRAL LINKS FOR HRC FUSEBS88 NEUTRAL LINKS FOR HRC FUSE
BS88 OFFSET BOLTED TAG FUSES 16AMP TO 200AMP TYPE 94mm FIXING CENTRESTYPE TCP,CEO,DEO
BS88 OFFSET BOLTED TAG FUSES 2AMP TO 100AMP TYPE 44.5mm AND 73mm FIXING CENTRESTYPE AAO BAO TIS OSD NITD STD
BS88 STREET LIGHTING FUSES AND FUSE HOLDERBS88 STREET LIGHTING FUSES TYPE LST,STD,MD,SMD
BUSSMANN
170M FUSESBUSSMANN 170M FUSE RANGE
BUSSMANN (EATON)
RED SPOT BS88 FUSE HOLDERS FORMERLY GEC AND GERED SPOT
(RS) SAFECLIP (SC) BS88
BUSSMANN (EATON) BS88 FUSE HOLDERSSAFELOC TYPE NNS.ENSF.CAMASTER TYPE CM FUSEHOLDERS BS88
BUSSMANN (EATON) FORMERLY GE POWER TRACTION FUSE/DC APPLICATIONBUSSMANN (EATON)/GE POWER TAC TYPE TRACTION FUSES
BUSSMANN (EATON) FORMERLY GE POWER XF.XS TYPE FUSESType
XF. XS. FUSES
BUSSMANN (EATON) SEMICONDUCTOR BS88 RANGE
FUSESCT ET FE FEE FM FMM LCT LET
EUROPEAN CYLINDRICAL FUSES.FUSEHOLDERS AND FUSE KITSAM GL 8x31 10x38 14x51 22x58
FERRAZ- MERSEN AMERICAN OBSOLETE FUSEAMERICAN STYLE OBSOLETE FUSES
FUSEHOLDERS/SPARES MEM (EATON) AND BILLMEM (EATON) BILL FUSEHOLDERS AND SPARES
House Service Cut Out Units AND FUSES (HENLEY AND LUCY) FOR MORE DETAILED RANGE PLEASE USE WEBSITE www.tfcutilitiesproducts.comSERIES 5-6-7-8 +ACCES
MERSEN (FERRAZ) AMERICAN & MIDGET TYPE FUSESBussman Littlefuse Ferraz
MERSEN (FERRAZ) AMERICAN TYPE HSJ - TYPE - J TD
FUSES AND FUSE HOLDERS(MERSEN ) A4J AJT
HSJ
LP-SP JKS
MERSEN (FERRAZ) BOTTLE TYPE FUSES STYLE NEO ZD16 D27 D33 D125 D01 D02
MERSEN (FERRAZ) BS88 FUSEHOLDER32AMP TO 125AMP FUSEHOLDER
MERSEN (FERRAZ) CYLINDRICAL (FERRULE) SEMICONDUCTOR
FUSEMERSEN (FERRAZ) 10X38 / 14X51 / 22X58MM 27X60 (URD/GRB/GRC/URC/URL)
MERSEN (FERRAZ) NH0 GL/GG TYPE 500VAC/250VDC 120KA/80KA EUROPEAN FUSEMERSEN (FERRAZ) NH0 GL/GG TYPE EUROPEAN FUSE
MERSEN (FERRAZ) NH0.NH00.NH000.NH1.NH2.NH3 AM TYPE 690VAC 80KA EUROPEAN BLADE FUSESMERSEN NH0.NH00.NH000.NH1.NH2.NH3 AM TYPE EUROPEAN FUSES
MERSEN (FERRAZ) NH00/NH000 SIZE AND SIZE GL/GG TYPE 500VAC/250VDC 120KA/80KA EUROPEAN FUSEMERSEN (FERRAZ) NH00/NH000 GL/GG TYPE EUROPEAN FUSE
MERSEN (FERRAZ) NH1 GL/GG TYPE 500VAC/250VDC 120KA/80KA EUROPEAN FUSEMERSEN (FERRAZ) NH1 GL/GG TYPE EUROPEAN FUSE
MERSEN (FERRAZ) NH2 SIZE AND.NH3 SIZE GL/GG TYPE 500VAC/250VDC 120KA/80KA EUROPEAN FUSEMERSEN (FERRAZ) NH2.NH3
GL/GG TYPE EUROPEAN FUSE
MERSEN (FERRAZ) SEMI-CONDUCTOR SQUARE BODY STYLE FUSESPC30/31/32/33 PC/71/72/73
MERSEN (FERRAZ) SEMICONDUCTOR
HIGH SPEED TYPE NH
EUROPEAN FUSEMERSEN (FERRAZ) CLASS GR/GRD/GS
MERSEN (FERRAZ)PHOTOVOLTAIC FUSES AND FUSE HOLDERS SOLAR POWERMERSEN SOLAR POWER
FUSES FUSEHOLDERS AND PHOTOVOLTAIC PRODUCTS
MERSEN FORMERLY FERRAZ SHAWMUT FORM 101 AMERICAN ROUND SEMICONDUCTOR FUSEAmerican Round FORM101
MERSEN MULTIBLOC NH FUSE SWITCH DISCONNECT HOLDERSNH 000/00/NH1/NH2/NH3 FUSE DISCONNECT MULTIBLOC
MINATURE FUSES AND FUSE KITS/FUSEHOLDERS (Glass/Ceramic)Glass And Ceramic FUSES AND FUSE KITS 5x20/5x25/6.3X32 SIZES
MULTI METER FUSEMULTI METER FUSES SIBA AND MERSEN FORMERLY FERRAZ
PILLAR J TYPE FUSES AND FUSEHOLDERS 83mm and 92mmMJ25/30/31 PJ30/31 JPU/JSU TYPE J
POLESTAR (C50
DIFFERENT BRANDS MCB AND RCBO AND RCD/RCCB NOT LISTEDGET B TYPE 6KA 1POLE MCB
EATON (MEM) (MOELLER) MCCBGEE NZMB1
EATON (MEM) MEMERA (NEW RANGE) 6KA EAD MCB /RCBO/RCCDEAD (NEW RANGE 6KA)
RCBODPE100 SINGLE POLE DDICE
GE MCB RANGE EP,SERIES E ,DGCP60 DG60 EP60 EP100 EP103 ASTER CONTAX SWITCHES RCCD
Ottermill/Simplex/Mitsubishi MCBType TM9
SCHNEIDER ACTI 9 IC60 (MERLIN GERIN) RCBOA9D108 /AD9318TYPE B /TYPE C RCBO
SCHNEIDER SQUARE D
QOE RCBO AND QO MCB RANGESCHNEIDER SQUARE D QO MCB
SCHNEIDER SQUARE D EAZY 9 RANGE MCB AND RCBOEZ9D
RCBO EZ9F MCB FORMERLY DOM RANGE
SCHNEIDER SQUARE D RESI9 RANGE R9D,R9F AND R9R MCB,RCBO AND RCDR9D R9F R9R MCB,RCBO,RCD FORMERLY SQO RANGE
SCHNEIDER SQUARE D SE IKQE IKQ KQE RCBO AND MCB RANGESCHNEIDER SQUARE D SE IKQ RANGE FORMERLY KQ RANGE
Privacy Policy
This policy covers the use of personal information collected when you use this site.From time to time, you may be asked to submit personal information about yourself (e.g. name and email address) in order to receive or use services on our website. By entering your details in the fields requested, you enable us to provide you with the services you select. Whenever you provide such personal information, we will treat that information in accordance with this policy. When using your personal information we will act in accordance with current legislation and aim to meet current Internet best practice.The site uses sessions to track a user being logged in. Once the user logs in the server identifies the IP address of the user, the site can then identify the user to allow them to see the restricted areas. The session will timeout after a period of no activity or the browser window is closed or the logout button is pressed. No personal information is contained in the session, so it\'s very secure.In general, any information you provide will only be used by The Fuse Company and by its agents. Your information will be disclosed where we are obliged by law.We will hold your personal information on our systems for as long as you use the service you have requested, and remove it in the event that the purpose has been met. We will ensure that all personal information supplied is held securely, in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.
Addition to the above for GDPR MAY 2018 for personal information
HOW DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU
We obtain information about you when you make a online purchase from our website also contact enquries
WHAT TYPE OF INFORMATION IS COLLECTED FROM YOU
The personal information we collect are
name,address,email address,ip address,contact number.
HOW IS YOUR INFORMATION USED
We do not use your information we collect
we do not market or sell or rent to any third parties
we only keep information for order history and invoice/payment accounts
emails received via confirmation of order via the website are deleted from the system when a hard copy is printed
to access the order information from the website we are password protected in which 2 people within the company
have access to.
INFORMATION COLLECTED BY THE HOSTING COMPANY OF THE WEBSITE
The information from orders from the website which the host collects on the secure servers are password protected
and the information received are not used or sold to any third parties
We have checked their policy and they have the relevant procedures in place
IF YOU WISH TO REMOVE YOUR DATA AT ANY TIME PLEASE EMAIL admin@thefusecompany.com
REVIEW OF THIS POLICY
We keep this policy under regular review  Last updated MAY 2018
Thank you using The Fuse Company!
Telephone: (+44) 151 546 5816 Fax: (+44) 0151 546 8940
Email:
Head office: Unit 11 Invincible Way, Gillmoss Industrial Estate, Hermes Road, Liverpool, L11 OED, United Kingdom
Returns Policy | Privacy | Security | Delivery | Conversion Chart | PDF's | Site Map
